day 28
it is necessary to water the garden to give flower bro
I'm going now
repost my Passengers here in California
maintain always good quality of my product
to be able to deliver the best experience
it's good
I left a little box of happiness on each table
who is not seen is not remembered
this is an action to be able to validate the brand in here
some places you will put
will have more sales turnover than others know
and then it moves again man
it's selling more there
not selling here
get the product you are not selling from here
puts there face
and then you keep playing with organization,
you know
now i'm waiting for 1 bike to arrive
for us to exchange 1 idea and start work
there guy
how is your lemon
I'll leave the parade in your hand
the company t-shirt
thank you brother
until tomorrow
starts tomorrow
you won't believe it
just closed with bike delivery
now i will keep making my deliveries
this way man
I got a message on Instagram that the mine
she wants my Passengers
said guy
there's a hamburger here
and then I came at the hamburger
is waiting for her
but you don't understand the size of the hamburger no
old
and then brother
Tati and Gustavo are around
if i can put my tag here
dear hand
it's a lot more sale you know
there is no way to put thirty little boxes
in a giant place like this bro
arrives Gustavo went
brother Caio pleasure
I'm great this is Tati
let me explain to you what the idea is
I'm here making my deliveries here
there's still 1 confusion between revenue and profit
but day thirty i will open
the box here for you is missing
fix some things
but tell me which company you don't need
it's already getting dark and I'm going
because the is broken
follow that there are only two days left
tamo together